export const chapter = "Chapter - 18: Adverbs";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What does an Adverb add to the meaning of?",
          optionA: "Noun",
          optionB: "Adjective",
          optionC: "Verb",
          correctAnswer: "Adjective",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following sentences demonstrates the modification of an Adjective by an Adverb?",
          optionA: "The cat jumped.",
          optionB: "The cat jumped quickly.",
          optionC: "The cat is jumping.",
          correctAnswer: "The cat jumped quickly.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'I looked at the pen carefully,' what is the Adverb modifying?",
          optionA: "Noun",
          optionB: "Adjective",
          optionC: "Verb",
          correctAnswer: "Verb",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What do the words 'carefully,' 'brightly,' and 'merrily' modify in the given text?",
          optionA: "Nouns",
          optionB: "Adjectives",
          optionC: "Verbs",
          correctAnswer: "Verbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "According to the text, which Adverbs modify the meaning of other Adverbs?",
          optionA: "Fast and late",
          optionB: "Enough and always",
          optionC: "Brightly and merrily",
          correctAnswer: "Enough and always",
        },
        {
          question: "How are many Adverbs formed from Adjectives?",
          optionA: "By adding -ful",
          optionB: "By adding -ly",
          optionC: "By adding -ness",
          correctAnswer: "By adding -ly",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of an Adjective turned into an Adverb using the -ly suffix?",
          optionA: "Brave",
          optionB: "Beautiful",
          optionC: "Bravely",
          correctAnswer: "Bravely",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the purpose of an Adverb when modifying a Verb?",
          optionA: "It indicates a location.",
          optionB: "It tells how an action is done.",
          optionC: "It specifies a person.",
          correctAnswer: "It tells how an action is done.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the function of the words 'very,' 'quite,' and 'really' in the examples provided in the text?",
          optionA: "Modifying nouns",
          optionB: "Modifying verbs",
          optionC: "Modifying adjectives",
          correctAnswer: "Modifying adjectives",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is not mentioned as a common Adverb in the text?",
          optionA: "Everywhere",
          optionB: "Always",
          optionC: "Beautifully",
          correctAnswer: "Beautifully",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "An Adverb adds to the meaning of an ________, a ________ or another ________.",
          options: ["Noun", "Adjective", "Verb"],
          correctAnswer: "Adjective",
        },
        {
          question: "The cake was ________. The cake was quite ________.",
          options: ["Sweet", "Delicious", "Tasty"],
          correctAnswer: "Delicious",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The words: carefully, brightly, and merrily add something to the meaning of the ________: looked, is shining, and is dancing respectively.",
          options: ["Nouns", "Adjectives", "Verbs"],
          correctAnswer: "Verbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Many Adverbs are formed by adding ________ to Adjectives; for example:",
          options: ["-ful", "-ly", "-ness"],
          correctAnswer: "-ly",
        },
        {
          question: "The boy ran ________. The boy ran fast ________.",
          options: ["Slowly", "Quickly", "Loudly"],
          correctAnswer: "Quickly",
        },
        {
          question: "The child is dancing. The child is dancing ________.",
          options: ["Merrily", "Sadly", "Bravely"],
          correctAnswer: "Merrily",
        },
        {
          question: "The sun is shining. The sun is shining ________.",
          options: ["Darkly", "Brightly", "Softly"],
          correctAnswer: "Brightly",
        },
        {
          question: "The cake was very ________. The cake was quite ________.",
          options: ["Delicious", "Sweet", "Tasty"],
          correctAnswer: "Delicious",
        },
        {
          question: "She comes late. She comes ________ late.",
          options: ["Always", "Never", "Sometimes"],
          correctAnswer: "Always",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The words: fast and late are Adverbs, whose meanings are being modified by other words: ________ and ________ respectively.",
          options: [
            "Careful and Always",
            "Enough and Never",
            "Enough and Always",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Enough and Always",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "An Adverb modifies the meaning of an Adjective, a Verb, or another Adverb.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs are formed by adding -ly to Adjectives.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'I looked at the pen carefully,' the Adverb modifies the Noun.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs modify the meaning of Nouns.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The words 'fast' and 'late' can be Adverbs when their meanings are modified by other words.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Many Adverbs are formed by adding -ness to Adjectives.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In negative sentences in the Past Continuous Tense, 'not' is placed after the subject.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Past Continuous Tense sentences demonstrate the continuity of action in the Present.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In interrogative sentences, 'was' or 'were' is used in the beginning of the sentence along with the verb.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs modify the meaning of Adjectives but not Verbs.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
